<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gallery on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://aurokicrafts.ca/gallery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gallery on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 10:06:28 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://aurokicrafts.ca/gallery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Century-Modern Coffee Table</title>
      <link>https://aurokicrafts.ca/gallery/mcm_coffee_table/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 10:06:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aurokicrafts.ca/gallery/mcm_coffee_table/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h6 id=&#34;description&#34;&gt;Description&lt;/h6&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;margin-left: 1em;&#34;&gt; &#xA;&lt;p&gt;Add warmth and functionality to your living space with this handcrafted midcentury modern coffee table. Made from solid red oak, it showcases the wood’s striking grain patterns and rich, natural tones. The design features clean lines, tapered legs, and a smooth, durable finish for a timeless aesthetic. A spacious middle shelf offers convenient storage for books, magazines, or decor, blending style with practicality. This table is the perfect centerpiece for a living room, combining classic craftsmanship with everyday utility.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walnut-Stained Midcentury Modern Coffee Table</title>
      <link>https://aurokicrafts.ca/gallery/mcm_coffee_table_walnut_stained/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 10:06:28 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aurokicrafts.ca/gallery/mcm_coffee_table_walnut_stained/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h6 id=&#34;description&#34;&gt;Description&lt;/h6&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;margin-left: 1em;&#34;&gt; &#xA;&lt;p&gt;Elevate your living space with this handcrafted midcentury modern coffee table, expertly crafted from solid red oak and stained in a rich walnut color. The deep, warm tones enhance the wood’s natural grain, creating a timeless, sophisticated look. Designed with clean lines and iconic tapered legs, the table also features a spacious middle shelf for convenient storage. Perfect as a functional statement piece, it seamlessly blends style and utility, adding character and charm to any room.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
